253-778-0954 iandillon1979@gmail.com 806 77th DR SE, Lake Stevens, WA 98258

# **Profile**

I have nearly 20 years of experience between the Travel and Aerospace industries and pride myself on providing exemplary customer service. I am a creative problem solver, hold myself to a high standard of quality and have experience in communicating effectively with a wide range of personality styles.

# Experience

### INSIDE SALES SUPPORT (PART TIME) - HYDRO SYSTEMS USA - 2014-2018

- Order entry and follow up.
- Quote and quote follow up.
- Special projects (quoting large packages, coordinating MRO conference for outside sales team).

### **CUSTOMER SERVICE MANAGER - HYDRO SYSTEMS USA - 2011-2013**

- Ensure the smooth running of inside sales team, as well as resolving any conflict.
- Worked closely with VP of sales for entry into service packages and price points to remained competitive.
- Worked with worldwide sales team on large tooling packages.
- Coordinate shipments of engine transportation stands and large tooling orders.
- Worked closely with planning, production and purchasing to ensure open orders were supported and to proactively
  advise customers of potential delays.
- Quote and order entry.
- Dealing with complaints and potential AOG situations.
- Running monthly/quarterly reports ranging from agent commissions, open orders, pricing analysis and sales input numbers.
- Manage inventory program.

### ORDER ENTRY/TEAM LEAD - TMX AEROSPACE - 2009-2011

- Consistently high order entry numbers with minimal error.
- Order review for new employees.
- Run monthly material reports and work with purchasing to ensure open orders were met.
- Handle AOG and line stopper situations

### CUSTOMER SERVICE MANAGER/SENIOR TRAVEL CONSULTANT - AERO24 - 2001-2008

- Ensure the smooth running of the call center as well as resolve any conflict.
- Run monthly reports to ensure key metrics where met.
- Write and update work instructions.
- Book emergency travel arrangements for stranded passengers.

# Education

Orpington College, Orpington, Kent, United Kingdom 1994-1996 GNVQ Leisure and Tourism

# Skills

During my travel career I used all major computer reservation systems, Galileo, Sabre, Worldspan and Amadeus. While in Aerospace I have used many ERP systems including SAP, ISS (inside sales), ProAlpha and MASS (material and service systems), I also have experience with the Boeing portal, ITEM, Boeing drawings, excel and MS word.

# References

Andy Blay (206) 595-9337

Jon Edwards (425) 654-9625